LOAN DO

Hello! My name is Loan and I'm 28 years old. I used to work in communication, but I've been retraining into web-programming for the past year. Thus, I'm looking for an apprenticeship for a year starting fall 2020.

My languages: RUBY, JAVASCRIPT, SQL, CSS & HTML5.

www.github.com/janelane666 https://loandoes.com



EDUCATION

Ada Tech School / Feb 2019 - Oct 2021
Full-Stack Programming School
Projects done in : CSS, HTML5, Ruby, Python,
Javascript, Vue, Processing, SQL, ULM

The Hacking Project / Sept 2019 - Dec 2019
Full-Stack Web Programming Bootcamp
Projects done in : CSS, HTML5,
Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL

Sciences Po Lille / Sept 2014 - June 2016
Master « Public and Corporate Communication »
Final year dissertation :
« Sneakers ; from sport to culture »

Sciences Po Lille / Sept 2010 - June 2013 Bachelor in Political Sciences

SKILLS

IT : Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Google Suite, Notion, Git, Asana, Miro

> Methodologies : Agile, TDD, Retrospective Languages : French, English, Vietnamese

INTERESTS

Food, Electronic Music, (I organized small private music festivals), biking, DJing.

EXPERIENCE

KissKissBankBank - Chief Happiness Officer

Nov 2017 - Abril 2019 / Paris

- · Office management
- Internal communication & events
- Creative assistant

Atelier Annam - Manager

March 2017 - Nov 2017 / Paris

Opening of a Vietnamese restaurant with my family.

KissKissBankBank - Project Specialist (Internship)

Feb 2016 - Aug 2016 / Paris

- · Tutoring crowdfunding campaigns
- Speaker in crowdfunding's events
- · Support et customer service

Opening Ceremony - Showroom Assistant (Internship)

Oct 2013 - June 2014 / New York

- Office management
- · Account management assistant
- Events organisation (casting, runaways, private sales).

Shortguide - Development Assistant (Internship)

July - Aug 2013 / Paris

- Community Management
- Benchmarks & user tests
- · Partnerships with bloggers

EXTRACURRICULAR

Sciences Po Lille Model United Nations : Head Delegate Sciences Po Lille Junior Entreprise : Communication